businessbroker.net 2019-01-26

# Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, Disclaimer | BusinessBroker.net

Summary of Key Points

  * By submitting an Information Request form, you also agree to receive e-mails, phone calls, and text messages from BusinessBroker.net (BBN) and those businesses for which you requested information. Communication from BBN is only used to confirm your request.
  * By providing your e-mail address to BBN on the Request Information Form (from specific businesses for sale or franchises for sale), you are agreeing to receive e-mails from BBN that showcase new franchises, businesses for sale, and other relevant entrepreneurial information. You may Unsubscribe from these e-mails at any time by clicking on the one-step Unsubscribe link found in these e-mails.
  * The e-mail contact forms on our website are only to be used to send inquiries about buying a particular business for sale, franchise, or business opportunity. By submitting your information, you expressly confirm that you have a genuine interest in each of the concepts for which you have requested information. These forms are not to be used to promote a business, service, or other concept.
  * Spamming of any sort on our site is not permitted as it hurts the integrity, credibility, and value of our business. Moreover, it jeopardizes our ability to continue to provide our services to legitimate users. By using the website and submitting a contact form you agree with these conditions.

FOR ADVERTISERS

Listing Services

Listing services provided by BusinessBroker.net (BBN) are provided “As Is”. Clients of any of these services, or “advertisers” are responsible for the information posted on the site and are responsible for monitoring and managing their own accounts. In no way is BusinessBroker.net responsible for this information. Purchasers or users of these services also agree that all information provided to BusinessBroker.net or posted on BusinessBroker.net is accurate and is in no way misleading. It is the full responsibility of BBN’s clients or “advertisers” to monitor this information. BusinessBroker.net does reserve the right to modify, change, reject, delete, or update any information provided on the site by a listing service or advertising client. BusinessBroker.net also reserves the right to modify, upgrade, or change our listing service(s) features in any way with or without notice. We also reserve the right to forward contact information from individual businesses who post businesses for sale on our website to business brokers, attorneys, merger and acquisition professionals, or other related service providers.

Intellectual Property Warranty, & Indemnification.

Advertiser (Business Broker, For Sale By Owner (FSBO), Franchise, Supplier, and Agency if applicable) represents that the subject matter, copy, and graphics of advertisements submitted for publication on BBN by Advertiser do not violate any applicable law and that Advertiser and agency are authorized to have same published. Further, the Advertiser affirms that they have secured all third party consents, licenses, and waivers and permissions necessary to display the ad content (including photos) placed on the website(s). Advertiser and agency agree to indemnify, hold harmless and defend at their own expense BBN, its officers, employees, directors, and owners from any liability, loss, and expense (including, but not limited to, court costs and attorney's fees) arising out of publication by BBN of any information and/or advertisement, including but not limited to any claim or lawsuit for libel, plagiarism, copyright or trademark infringement, franchisee disputes (including but not limited to, all costs from litigation associated with BBN, or its officers, employees, directors and owners being named party to litigation which is or resulting from advertising which franchisee(s) claim was false or misleading), and any and all litigation related to the Advertiser’s use of contact lead information and/or any inquiry by a prospective franchisee or business opportunity owner supplied by BBN to Advertiser.

Advertising Categorization - Search Function

BusinessBroker.net reserves the right to modify and re-classify any advertising listing on the site at any time by adding new industry related categories, removing industry related categories, or modifying or adjusting any other classifications system that defines where or how a user will find a listed company's ads. These changes may alter the way a listing advertisement is found through the website's various search functions and tools.

Payment of Services - Subscriptions

Payment of services is due prior to the activation of any advertising service. According to the periodic billing plan you choose, Business Broker, Agent, and other Directory membership accounts/listings are considered subscriptions that will be billed to your credit card on an ongoing basis. To cancel any subscription prior to additional billing, simply Contact Us via our Contact Form. Pricing for these memberships is subject to change with or without notice. It is the responsibility of the advertising/subscription/membership/listing purchaser to cancel their advertising to avoid any additional periodical subscription charges. Declined credit card authorizations, bad checks, or bad payments may be subject to a service fee that will be determined by BusinessBroker.net. BusinessBroker.net reserves the right to increase prices for any of its listing services, membership services, or other products at any time with or without notice. It is the subscriber/members responsibility to monitor the current prices on our website for our listing services and to cancel their subscription/membership if they do not wish to pay.

Franchise advertising on BBN is managed via [Franchise Opportunities Network (FON)](https://www.franoppnetwork.com/) and FON payment policies apply.

Refund Policy

BusinessBroker.net is in no way obligated to refund any money for any service purchases after the actual service has been activated or implemented.

Service Problems or Interruptions

BusinessBroker.net relies on an outside vendor for website hosting and some technology solutions. BusinessBroker.net is not responsible for any website downtime or service interruptions associated with any technology problem(s), Internet problem(s), or any other type of problem(s) and is in no way obligated to make monetary reimbursements or refunds for any reason.

Privacy Policy for Advertisers

When you advertise on BusinessBroker.net we ask for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and other information. This information is sometimes displayed to users of our websites in order to generate leads. BusinessBroker.net or our business partners and sponsors may use your information to contact you about services and opportunities, to take surveys, and to offer other related services. In addition to your contact information, we may also ask for your credit card number. Your credit card number will remain confidential and will only be used for proper billing purposes. By agreeing with these terms you agree that we may use and store your information, including credit card information, in accordance with this privacy policy. You are not permitted to use our services unless you agree with these terms.

FOR SITE USERS

All BusinessBroker.net site users and service customers agree and understand that BusinessBroker.net is in no way providing any legal, accounting, or business advice relating to the purchase or sale of any business or franchise, the hiring of any service advertiser, or the purchase of any products advertised on the website. We strongly recommend that all users consult with a qualified third party not associated with BusinessBroker.net prior to engaging in any of these activities. We are merely a lead generating advertising service for our clients.

Request Form & Contact Form Usage Policy

Users are permitted to use the email contact forms and/or our lead submission forms only for the purpose to gain further information from the business for sale, franchisor and/or business opportunity. The email contact forms and/or lead submission forms on our website are only to be used to send inquiries about buying a particular business for sale, franchise, or other related business opportunity. By submitting your information you expressly confirm that you have a genuine interest in each of the concepts for which you have requested information; that you wish for a representative from each of the concepts to contact you; and that the information that you have submitted is true and correct.

We are grateful that you have taken the time to come to our site and inquire about the exciting businesses for sale, franchises, and business opportunities we have listed. In order to provide the best service possible to both you and our clients we must insist that you respect and understand this Policy. By submitting your information you expressly agree to receive a phone call, text message, or e-mail message from the entity from whom you requested information. BBN may also contact you to confirm your request for more information via phone, email, or text message.

Submitting contact information that is either false or is done without interest to the particular business for which you have submitted your information is called “spamming”. Spamming of any sort on our site is not permitted as it hurts the integrity, credibility, and value of our business. Moreover, it jeopardizes our ability to continue to provide our services to legitimate users. Unauthorized use of the email contact forms to contact advertisers or “spamming” on our website will be billed to the responsible party at a rate of $1,000 per unauthorized contact. By using the website and submitting a contact form you agree with these conditions.

Collection & Use of Information from Site Users

You may browse our website at any time without providing your contact and/or personal information. If, however, you are interested in a particular business for sale, franchise, service, opportunity and/or any additional information from BusinessBroker.net (and/or our advertisers) you may register with us and provide your personally identifiable information, which is information that, alone or in combination with other information, allows us to identify you, such as your name, address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, financial information or information relating to a support or service issue. Any and all lead and contact information submitted to BusinessBroker.net is forwarded directly to our database; and thus any and all lead and contact information BusinessBroker.net collects remains the property of BusinessBroker.net. We may also use this information to send you (or have sent to you) additional information about other business opportunities/service providers that we determine may fit your criteria. BusinessBroker.net and/or its advertisers may also contact you for other business purposes, such as to conduct surveys or to offer business consulting/coaching services or related services. Please note that each franchisor and/or service provider is responsible for its own privacy practices.

We share your information with the franchises and business for sale opportunities in which you have expressed interest. If you no longer want to receive information from a franchise or business opportunity, please contact that franchise or business for sale or business broker directly.

If you provide us with your personally identifiable information, you are giving us permission to use that information for the specific purpose for which it is provided and for any other purpose described in this Privacy Policy, which are described in detail below under “ **How We Use the Information** ”.  By providing us with personally identifiable information, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy. Users unwilling to provide personally identifiable information online can choose not to provide such information, and in some (but not all) situations users may be able to work with a sales representative or customer service representative to utilize our Services or other offerings without providing personally identifiable information.  In addition, if you do provide us with your personally identifiable information, you have the ability to prevent us from sharing your information with third parties if you wish, as described below under “ **Your Options Regarding Personally Identifiable Information** ”.

We also may collect, store and use certain non-personally identifiable information we receive when you use our Services, and we may aggregate data and information provided by or collected from multiple users (which may include you) in a manner that is not personally identifiable to any individual user.  All non-personally identifiable information collected by us through our Services and all aggregated/compilations of data we create are the exclusive property of BBN.  Nothing in this Privacy Policy limits our right to use any such non-personally identifiable or aggregated information in any way (including, but not limited to, monitoring user traffic patterns, analyzing and quantifying user preferences, improving the design and content of our Services, and enabling us to personalize your user experience) or prohibits us from sharing non-personally identifiable or aggregated information with third parties.

How We Use the Information

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we share personally identifiable information collected through our Services with unaffiliated third parties only as described below.  (Please see “ **Your Options Regarding Personally Identifiable Information** ” below for information on how to avoid having your personally identifiable information shared by us.)

  * _Third Party Service Providers_ :  We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and providing customer service. In connection with their performance of functions on our behalf, we may share personally identifiable information with such companies and individuals as needed for them to perform their functions, but we do not permit such entities and individuals to use personally identifiable information for other purposes.
  * _Business Transfers_ :  As we continue to develop our business we might sell or buy companies, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, personally identifiable information is generally one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that we are acquired or assigned, personally identifiable information will be one of the transferred assets. In such event, this Privacy Policy may be amended as set forth below or the collection and uses of your personally identifiable information may be governed by a different privacy policy.
  * _Protection of Our Services and Others_ :  We reserve the right to release personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of BBN, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other unaffiliated third parties in connection with fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * _With Your Consent_ :  Other than as set out above, you will receive notice and have the opportunity to withhold consent when personally identifiable information about you might be shared with unaffiliated third parties.
  * _User Submissions_ :  If you participate in any online forum/communities, chat sessions and/or blogs, or otherwise post in any user comment field visible to other users of our Services, any information that you submit or post will be visible to and may be read, collected or used by others who use our Services.  We are not responsible for any information, including personally identifiable information, you choose to submit in any such user comment field.

Your Options Regarding Personally Identifiable Information

Except where we believe the release of your personally identifiable information is necessary or appropriate (a) to allow third party service providers to perform functions on our behalf or (b) to comply with law, enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of BBN, our users or others, you may opt out of our sharing your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties by contacting us directly via our Contact Us Form on our website. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

Third Party Online Advertising

We sometimes partner with third party ad networks to manage our advertising on other sites. An ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests (interest-based ads). For more information on this practice, or to opt out of having this information used by these companies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative here on [this webpage:](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by following the directions below. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

To opt-out of interest-based ads, personalized ads, and/or Google's use of cookies on Google, go to this [Google Ad Settings webpage](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) and make a selection next to "Opt-Out Settings" to prevent targeted advertising on Google's own sites, or across the web.

To opt-out of interest-based ads on Facebook, go to [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) in the USA, [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada](http://youradchoices.ca/) in Canada or the [European Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) in Europe and select "Facebook Inc." from the list.

Google® AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site or to audiences similar to people who have visited our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or on sites across the internet in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to a website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) to opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or [permanently using a browser plugin.](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin?hl=en)

Cookies

We also collect and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our website server, and to administer our website. We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer or mobile device’s browser for record-keeping purposes. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or reveal other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one or more of our websites. However, once you choose to furnish us with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics to improve our Web site.

Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Services, Ad Servers and Sponsors

Our Services may contain links to other websites or services whose information practices may be different than ours. For example, while using one or more of our websites, you may link to a third party’s website via a window opened within (or on top of) our website. Some of our Services may allow users to interface with third party websites or services, such as Facebook and Twitter. You will remain logged into those third party websites or services until you actively log off. By interfacing with those third party websites or services, you are allowing our Services to access your information that is or becomes available via such third party websites or services, and you are agreeing to those third party’s applicable terms and conditions. Once you log onto any such third party websites or services, the content you post there may also post to our Services. Our Privacy Policy and procedures may or may not be consistent with the policies and procedures of such third party websites or services, and when you visit such websites or services our Privacy Policy does not apply to personally identifiable information and other data collected by the third party. You should consult, read and understand the privacy notices of such third parties before choosing to provide personally identifiable information on any such websites or services.

E-Mail Newsletter Marketing

BBN does send e-mails providing franchise and business for sale updates and entrepreneur related articles to users who have provided BBN their e-mail address. If you wish to UNSUBSCRIBE from our e-mails, please follow the simple Unsubscribe instructions which are located at the bottom of each e-mail. If for some reason the Unsubscribe function does not work please Contact Us via our website.

Mobile Apps & Location Information

When you download or use our mobile Application (the “apps”), we may collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices' unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use and information about the way you use the apps. The apps may also collect precise information about your device's real-time location (from cell towers or global positioning system technology (“GPS”)). This information is used to provide services like localized search results and to market certain of our products and services to you. You can disable location-sharing at any time in your device settings. We also use an encrypted version of your device's unique device ID to track app usage and to send any mobile alerts that you ask to receive.

California Do Not Track Notice

Certain websites and other technology can track their users over time to, for instance, provide targeted advertising. Do Not Track (“DNT”) mechanisms allow Internet users to control, and where desired, prevent the tracking of their online activities across such websites and technology. Currently, various Internet browsers offer a DNT option that sends signals to websites visited by the browser about the user's DNT preference – you can usually access your browser's DNT option in your browser's preferences. Specifically as DNT relates to your use of our Services, we currently do not have the capability to recognize or respond to web browser Do Not Track signals and other similar mechanisms. In addition, in the DNT context, other parties do not have the ability to collect your personally identifiable information through advertising technologies deployed in ads that may appear within our Services.

Canada's Anti-Spam Law

Commercial electronic messages that are sent from or accessed in Canada, including emails and text messages (“CEMs”), are governed by Canada's Anti-Spam Law and its relevant rules and regulations (“CASL”). CASL requires that any CEMs sent to Canadian recipients in connection with our Services comply with certain consent and informational requirements (generally speaking, CASL prohibits sending CEMs to Canadian recipients without the prior consent of the recipient). Consent may either be implied (which is temporary) or express (which is permanent, unless and until withdrawn). Examples of implied consent to receive CEMs include (i) your having purchased something from us within the past two years, (ii) your download of software included within our Services or (iii) your giving us your business card at a trade show. You provide express consent when you affirmatively elect to receive CEMs in response to a clear solicitation to do so (for instance, filling out a form on one of our websites where the form clearly states that you will receive CEMs from BBN). When applicable, BBN will ask for your express consent to receive CEMs, and will respect your decision. Under any circumstances, however, you have the right to withdraw your consent – whether express or implied – by following the instructions to unsubscribe found in emails sent to you or by contacting us via the contact information provided below.

Our Commitment to Security

We have in place what we believe to be reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access of, maintain data security for and correctly use the personally identifiable information you have provided or that we otherwise collect through our Services. However, while such efforts are intended to ensure the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information available to us as a result of your use of our services, we cannot and do not warrant or guarantee the absolute safety and security of your personally identifiable information.

  * We work to protect the security of your personally identifiable information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. To assist in keeping your personally identifiable information safe, you must use an SSL-enabled browser (i.e., Internet Explorer).
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password, your computer and your mobile device(s). Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. Additionally, change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure Web browser.

Questions/Concerns and How You Can Access or Correct Information

If you have questions or concerns, please contact us via contact information below. Also, you may obtain information regarding the personally identifiable information that you provide or we collect about you via our Services for the limited purpose of viewing and correcting any factual errors in such information. Access to personally identifiable information that you provide or we collect via our Services may be accessible for a limited period of time after the point of collection. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our Services, you may return to that portion of the Services to review the personally identifiable information you provided. Alternatively, you may send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting information about or corrections to your personally identifiable information subject to appropriate verification procedures.

**Business Broker Network  
375 Northridge Road, Suite 475  
Atlanta, GA 30350  
Toll Free: 877-342-9786**

E-Mail – [tglasgow@businessbroker.net](mailto:tglasgow@businessbroker.net) or CONTACT US via Web Form

To protect your privacy and security, we will take what we believe are reasonable steps to help verify your identity before providing personally identifiable information, granting access or making corrections.

Miscellaneous Advertisers in our Franchise Channels

Please note that not all of the advertisers in the various franchise advertising channels on BusinessBroker.net are legally a franchise. Some of the companies that advertise in these channels are dealership opportunities or other business related opportunities. BusinessBroker.net recommends seeking the advice of a lawyer, business consultant, financial advisor, and accountant before purchasing any of these opportunities.

GENERAL – APPLICABLE TO ALL

Business Brokers, Agents, Buyers, Independent Sellers, Franchises, Attorneys, and all other Site Advertisers

BusinessBroker.net is a lead generating advertising service. Business brokers, agents, business buyers, independent business sellers, franchise companies, attorneys, finance companies, and all other advertisements and listings found on the BusinessBroker.net website are simply advertising purchasers, listing service purchasers, or other advertising clients and are not employed by or otherwise affiliated with BusinessBroker.net. BusinessBroker.net is in no way responsible for their actions, representations, or business dealings. BusinessBroker.net reserves the right to identify these service clients as “members”, “subscribers”, “affiliates”, “advertisers” or any other related description. Business brokers, agents, franchise companies or other intermediary's who post business for sale listings for their clients or companies on our website assume all responsibility for these listings and acknowledge that they have the authority, granted by their client, to post these listings.

Non Disclosure Agreement

Site users, advertisers, and broker & agent members are required to keep all dealings between BusinessBroker.net and themselves strictly confidential. Site users acknowledge that the sharing of any information, gathered as a result of using our online service, with others could negatively impact our business. Site users agree to be held responsible for any financial damages that BusinessBroker.net may incur as a result of this type of behavior. Any monetary damages will be determined and set by BusinessBroker.net. Employees of other industry related franchise or business for sale sites and businesses are not allowed to use BusinessBroker.net under any circumstance without the express written consent of BusinessBroker.net management. If you do not agree with our Non-Disclosure Agreement terms then you are not permitted to use our services under any circumstance.

Illegal Usage - Database Reproduction & Information Gathering

The reproduction of the BusinessBroker.net database in any way is strictly prohibited without the expressed written consent of the BusinessBroker.net executive management. The use of information located in the BusinessBroker.net database in any unauthorized sales, information gathering, or any other marketing related initiative is strictly prohibited. The use of this website for any of these reasons without the expressed written consent of BusinessBroker.net executive management is illegal and will be aggressively defended in the court system. If we find that any person, business, company, or other entity has used the website for any of these reasons then the party responsible will agree to pay BusinessBroker.net a fee of up to $2,000,000, which will be determined by the BusinessBroker.net executive management depending on the severity of the infringement. Unauthorized use of the email contact forms to contact advertisers on our website will be billed to the responsible party at a rate of $1,000 per unauthorized contact. By using the website you agree with these conditions. If you have trouble understanding these terms then we suggest that you seek the advice of a lawyer.

Copyrights and Intellectual Property Rights

The content on the BusinessBroker.net website is copyrighted © 2017 by Business Broker Network, Inc. and all rights are reserved. Any unauthorized reproduction is strictly prohibited. All BusinessBroker.net services, logos, publications, trademarks, service marks, software, and formats is the property of BusinessBroker.net and is not to be reproduced in any way without the written consent of BusinessBroker.net executive management. Users of the website may print information found on this site only for non-commercial, personal, regular use.

Children's Policy

BBN is intended to be used by individuals over the age of 18. We do not seek or willingly collect information on children under the age of 18. If we discover that we have collected information on a child under the age of 13, then we will delete that information from our system.

Links to Other Websites

BusinessBroker.net may link to other websites, which is done for your convenience and information only, and occasionally other websites may be co-branded with our trade names and trademarks. Websites that are linked to our websites or carry our brands may have privacy policies which differ from ours, and which we do not control. In no way is BusinessBroker.net responsible for the content, representations, advertising, or anything else found on these websites and has no control over this information. Users of the BusinessBroker.net website visit these sites under their own risk.

Affiliate Website

BusinessBroker.net expects to receive site users and listing service purchases from traffic delivered from partner and affiliate websites. BusinessBroker.net is not responsible for any false or misleading claims made by affiliates or partners. Refunds made to these customers, for any reason, will only be completed after BusinessBroker.net receives a full and equal refund from the affiliate or partner website that was paid a commission to deliver the listing service purchaser.

Jurisdiction and Legal Issues

The use of the BusinessBroker.net website or its services is governed by the laws of the State of Georgia. Any enforcement of the BusinessBroker.net terms or disclaimer will be brought in the state or federal courts located in Atlanta, Georgia. Any claim against BusinessBroker.net will also be required to be brought in the state or federal courts located in Atlanta, Georgia. BusinessBroker.net reserves the right to request and to receive an arbitration hearing for any claims brought against the company, its officers, management, owners, or employees by any site users, clients, or other parties that will be fully paid for by the person(s), company(s), or organization(s) making the claim. Any arbitration hearing will be held in Atlanta, Georgia. The use of the BusinessBroker.net website or any of its services signifies that you agree with these terms and disclaimer. If you do not agree with these terms and disclaimer then you are not permitted to use the BusinessBroker.net website or any of our services. We recommend that you hire an attorney if you need assistance understanding these terms.

Newsletter, Magazines, and other Publications

All of the Terms of Use and Disclaimers outlined on this page apply to all BusinessBroker.net newsletters, magazines, publications, advertising, press releases, and other forms of communication.

Disclaimer

As noted in this Privacy Policy, we take our commitment to protection of your privacy seriously. However, nothing in this privacy policy is intended to create or provide any right of action for violation.

Account Holders

To protect the account information of our Website members, where applicable, BBN assigns to each member either a unique user name or password or a unique ad ID number. These unique identifiers are disclosed to the user via email immediately upon becoming a member of this Website. Only members have the ability to modify their personal information as needed.

If you become a member of this Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device, and you agree to and accept sole responsibility for any and all activities that occur under your account or password. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other breach of security, of which you become aware. However, you may be held liable for losses incurred by us or any other user of, or visitor to, this Website due to someone else using your account or password. Please see our Privacy Policy for further information regarding your account or password.

Ownership; License; Limitations

This Website and all content displayed on this Website and all software, data and information used to provide this Website, including text and images, method of display and presentation, source code, embedded routines and programs and other materials, as well as all copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights therein or thereto, are owned by BBN or our owners, affiliates, licensors or licensees, and are protected under worldwide patent, copyright, trademark and other applicable laws and treaties, including, without limitation, applicable trade secret laws. We grant you the limited and nonexclusive right and license to access or download a single copy of the content from this Website solely for your personal and non commercial use and as necessary in connection with the use of any services available through this Website.

Except as expressly authorized in these Terms and Conditions, you may not modify, distribute, reproduce, display, or use this Website or any elements thereof. Furthermore, (i) reproduction, re transmission or re presentation in any form, in whole or in part, of any content, programming code, images or graphics included within this Website is strictly prohibited without our prior express written permission; (ii) you may not frame, squeeze back, overlay or employ other techniques to enclose or display this Website, or any trademark, logo, content or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) included on this Website, with any other software or content of a third party; (iii) you may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing the names or trademarks of BBN or our owners, affiliates, licensors or licensees without our or their express written consent; and (iv) you may not decompile or disassemble, reverse engineer or otherwise attempt to discover any source code contained in this Website or the services offered herein.

In addition to and not in limitation of any of the foregoing limitations and restrictions, you are expressly prohibited from using automated means (including but not limited to spiders, robots, crawlers, scrapers, deep links, data mining, data gathering or extraction tools and the like), or any other automated methodology, algorithm or device or any manual process, for any purpose to monitor, copy, download or otherwise access data or content from this Website. A limited exception to the foregoing limitations and restrictions is provided to general purpose internet search engines and non-commercial public archives that use such tools to gather information for the sole purpose of displaying hyperlinks to this Website, provided they each do so from a stable IP address or range of IP addresses using an easily identifiable agent and comply with our applicable policies and procedures in effect from time to time. “General purpose internet search engine” does not include a website or search engine or other service that specializes in classified listings or in any subset of classifieds listings such as automobiles, vehicles, jobs, housing/apartments, rentals, services or equipment or which is in the business of providing classified ad listing services.

This Website includes certain trademarks and service marks owned by BBN and/or our owners, affiliates or others. You agree not to copy, use or otherwise infringe upon or dilute these trademarks or service marks. You further agree that you will not alter or remove any copyright, trademark or other notices from any of Website content.

All rights not expressly granted to you by us in these Terms and Conditions are reserved to BBN, and you acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by accessing or downloading any material, whether or not copyrighted, from this Website as authorized hereunder.

Data Security

We have in place what we believe to be reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access of, maintain data security for and correctly use the information we collect online. However, while such reasonable efforts are made to ensure the confidentiality of your private and personal information available as a result of your use of this Website, we cannot and do not warrant or guarantee the absolute safety and security of confidential data on the Internet.

Notification of Claims of Infringement

BBN respects the rights of all copyright holders and in this regard has adopted and implemented a policy that provides for the removal of content from this Website under certain circumstances. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide BBN’s Copyright Agent with the following information required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. 512:

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;
  * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party (e.g., address, telephone number and email address);
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material is unauthorized; and
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

For copyright inquiries, including notification of claims of infringement, please contact BBN's Copyright Agent at:

BusinessBroker.net, c/o Dominion Enterprises  
Intellectual Property Administrator  
P.O. Box 2576  
Norfolk, VA 23501  
or  
or  
757-351-7000.

Changes in this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, from time to time as we deem appropriate by posting such changes on this Website, as applicable. Any changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting unless otherwise indicated. We will not separately notify you that changes have been made, regardless of the scope and importance of the changes, and we encourage you to periodically check back and review these Terms and Conditions so that you always will know what terms and conditions apply to your access to and use of this Website, or our use of any User Content that you have posted on this Website or submitted to us. Your continued use of this Website and/or your submission of any User Content to us after such changes are posted will be deemed to constitute your agreement to and acceptance of such changes. This Website may change, and we may restrict access to, suspend or discontinue this Website, or any portion of this Website, at any time.

If you have any questions concerning any of the above please contact us at:

Customer Service c/o Teresa Glasgow BusinessBroker.net  
375 Northridge Road, Suite 475  
Atlanta, GA 30350  
1-877-342-9786
